<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[ChanzoHuru]]></title><description><![CDATA[A community club that is poised to spread and  foster collaboration and advancement of technology in our local communities]]></description><link>https://chanzohuru.or.tz</link><image><url>https://chanzohuru.or.tz/logos/icon.png</url><title>ChanzoHuru</title><link>https://chanzohuru.or.tz</link></image><generator>GatsbyJS Advanced Starter</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 10:49:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chanzohuru.or.tz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><copyright><![CDATA[© Copyright 2022 | ChanzoHuru]]></copyright><item><title><![CDATA[Jambo Dunia 👋🏽]]></title><description><![CDATA[We have started a community club called CHANZOHURU that is poised to spread and  foster collaboration and advancement of technology in our…]]></description><link>https://chanzohuru.or.tz/hello-world</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://chanzohuru.or.tz/hello-world</guid><category><![CDATA[programming]]></category><category><![CDATA[community]]></category><category><![CDATA[introduction]]></category><category><![CDATA[tech]]></category><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We have started a community club called CHANZOHURU that is poised to spread and  foster collaboration and advancement of technology in our local communities. We aim to achieve that by bringing joining together professionals, entrepreneurs, scientists and students in the ICT industry to solve local problems, educate (capacity building from millennials to new generations), share knowledge and inspire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We strongly believe in open collaboration and open source, so think of our community as a Venn diagram showing the intersection of STEM geeks coming together and see what challenges we can solve in our communities. If you’re a coder, designer, scientist, hacker or just an enthusiastic person with good ideas, You’re the chosen one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the objective of mobilizing the talents we have in our communities to learn, solve, develop, lobby and earn together in one conducive environment where we can upskill industry standards and set a new status quo &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the core benefits that we’re hoping to impact in our community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contribute ideas and be part of solving local problems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to community projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Professional networking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trainings and workshops&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to community info&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;This community is membership based that is renewed annually and we aim that the community will drive itself through the solution that will be built by the community members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h6&gt;&lt;span role=&quot;img&quot; aria-label=&quot;warning&quot;&gt;⚠️&lt;/span&gt; To join our community is by invitation only.&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;p&gt; To learn more email us  at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:karibu@chanzohuru.or.tz&quot;&gt;karibu@chanzohuru.or.tz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><author>karibu@chanzohuru.or.tz</author></item></channel></rss>